get it together gunky poops you're
playing like a 14-year-old with Down
Syndrome you're one talk hoarding all L
gold armor like a greedy Enderman hey
[__] I can't help it if I'm the master
of bling in a world of
blocks hey are you guys playing
Minecraft yep how about you let a girl
get in on the fun piss off [__] girls
can't play Minecraft yeah why do you
think Steve is a man okay
why are you mining on level 37 what do
you think we're looking for
diamonds diamonds spawn between levels
50 and
64 Sonia don't tell us that why it ruins
the fun you stupid [__] you are
correct brother girls will never
understand the nuances of real Discovery
that's why there hasn't been a single
important woman through all of human
history what about Pat Oli Sonia you are
pooping on my butt no one knows who that
is all I'm saying is you would have a
full set of armor by now if you just we
can't hear you
la hey Uncle
Chuck are
you I was about to leave my dle booty
cheeks however there's something I
wanted to ask you first okay well you
know how it's the last day of school no
well it is and our teacher is out sick
and I well I put in a good word for you
with our principal how would you like to
be our substitute teacher for the last
day of middle
school me you want me
with because it would be like we were
graduating together wouldn't it be fun
you
didn't so when he
went Andy anyway that's so sad Uncle
Chuck it is
[Music]
sad
no we got Spirit yes we do we got Spirit
how about
you pH what a workout that was nicely
done girls I can't tell you've all been
practicing especially you Sarah you were
pretty agile out there of course I was
I've been cheerleading since I was knive
to a grasshopper mama always said I had
more energy than a herd of wild mustangs
that's really cool Sarah everyone
remember to I'd be out there in the
fields cheering on them cows and horses
like they was fixing to win the rodeo my
palom poms will makeshift made him out
of ribbons I found lying around the barn
folks used to say Sarah you're like a
tumble weed in a wind storm Unstoppable
and I reckon they was right cuz no
matter where life done took me I always
kept cheerleading close to my heart
caruse when you're Sarah shut the [__]
up yo Flor don't you go anywhere just
yet is there a problem yes in fact there
is you were throwing off the rhythm of
the squad I I'm sorry Sonic I'm trying
my best but but it's just really hard
for me I don't want to hear your excuses
Flora you've been on this team long
enough to know the basics if you can't
keep up with me and the girls then maybe
you don't belong on this squad at all
you don't even wear the uniform that
dresses are so obscene and revealing why
can't I just wear my leaf you've had
your chance and you've blown it I can't
have someone like you dragging down the
team please pack up your things and
leave my
field now I want everyone to drink
plenty of water this afternoon we're
going to need to be hydrated like a man
summertime balls for tonight's
graduation
cheer hey you fat lard are you ready to
go back to class and put a school year
behind us okay then what are you waiting
for go change out of that leotard and
then come back so you can tell us about
that do Secret Surprise waiting for us
in the classroom
[Music]
would everyone please stand for today's
Pledge of
[Music]
Allegiance Al to the flag of the United
States of America and to the Republic
for which it stands one nation under God
indivisible of liy and justice
[Music]
what the hell was that what was what
that creepy cult like [__] where you all
stood up and chanted in unison I don't
know what you're talking
[Music]
about go after no student in Char your
substitute for tonight
ah bro what the hell is this why the
[__] is Uncle Chuck our substitute
teacher the principal said he was
looking for a replacement since our last
teacher was arrested via public
indecency around minors but he's not
smart enough to teach a middle school
class bro he's going to make himself
look like a dumbass [__] with special
needs that's the whole point it means
the last day of middle school is going
to go by so easy for us having this B
chz our tutor we're practically on
summer vacation already
super
smart wonderful world
of don't
they you haven't sex since I first
bananas
first Sonic is BL
and
what yes baby no
no I'm a bad
boy orange that's really good no no it's
not orang is not the correct answer hey
I was right the answer was yellow
y you did it manic you finally got a
question right this is the best day ever
baby pull down your pants I want to suck
your nuts no
no this
ising seriously who does this old man
think he is talking to us like that yeah
just because he's the uncle love bab's
[__] it doesn't mean he can't eat
leave the Nerds alone old man they
haven't done anything to you what you
got as a matter of fact I do they were
just saying Mr Chuck that maybe you
should stick to whatever it is you do
when you're not pretending to teach and
what exactly Domingo y kid stinky
Domingo well you're obviously goodl
looking with that hair ball on your face
and you've got that aome beer belly so
maybe you should just stick to being I
candy for the
ladies you can't make fun of us Chuck
we're kids yeah only we can make fun of
you I think you're pretty cool Uncle
Chuck thanks
appre as for the rest of
yours cool piss off then
[__] boy howdy Uncle Chuck brought beer
to school oh my uncle Chuck how could
you he's not a teacher he's is just a
fat drunk it would appear the great
uncle Chuck ain't so great after all
that's no go to the principal
immediately
and if you want to protect them so badly
they
sorry it's cool Jesus and those two
other guys did the same
thing hey Chuck did you know this your
last a just for rounding up cattle put
that away before I report you next y
don't you worry nun Uncle Chuck just
reckon I'd give you a taste of some good
old hillbilly
Hospitality you want
to in this classroom why Uncle Chuck
you're so bad at teaching I bet you
couldn't even teach a hog to squeal
let's see if you can fly though you fat
[__] hog smell my ass
that's it you are near report to the
principl office
immediately now you done made a big
mistake Mister Jared's my man and Nobody
messes with him without answering to me
S you have order order you call this
order you've done embarrass J R in front
of the whole class and for what CUA you
can't take a joke maybe it's you who
needs to learn a thing or two about resp
in folks around here you can't just go
send in folks to the principal's office
whenever you feel like it
what
okay your
wing I'm sorry Mr Chuck I was just
who that's not going to help you B this
class it's not a fairy tale it's the
Holy Bible and it really
happened that's not cool Uncle Chuck y
off her she has the right to practice
her religion anywhere she wants oh sorry
he didn't really say was
in hey that's too f far Uncle you're
making her cry
oh principle Peet you won't believe
what's happening you need to come to
your office right
away what's so important that you
interrupted my crap is it the usual
troublemakers causing
erus no it's not just a few students
this time it's it's an entire
[Applause]
classroom jumping flat Jacks what are
all of you doing here in my office
shouldn't you be in class preparing for
your graduation it's the new substitute
teacher Uncle Juck he's totally lost it
he's sending students to the principal's
office over nothing please make him stop
Mr fed buts so we can return into the
wonderful world of learning well I don't
know exactly what's going on here but
I'll get to the bottom of this by having
a word with your
[Music]
teacher what isent
into Uncle chunk may I speaked with your
assary
check where are the rest of the
kids but lunch isn't for two more
hours well can you explain to me why is
73% of your classes crammed in my office
like sardines
students sending an entire class to my
office for punishment is hardly minor I
think it's best if we had a chat in my
office you going anywhere
with then you left me no choice but to
contact security and have you escorted
off the premises by force
problem this
class so principal fat
[Music]
boot no no Mr Chunk it's it would seem
there's been quite the misunderstanding
the kids seem to have gotten a little
carried away with their stories but I'll
sort it out this content your Whispers
do know Whispers can't turn into suit Mr
fat
Mr TR I assure you there won't be any
problems between us I value the peace
and stability you brought to this school
and our
[Music]
community
students welcome me students it your
little visit with the principal
was and as a reward for
your but Uncle Chuck this isn't fair
this was supposed to be the biggest test
of the year that's right it counts for
40% of our grade do you want us to
repeat the eighth grade all over again
[Applause]
[Laughter]
Go uncle if I knew it would come to this
I never would have
what oh I see it's On's fault we're all
going to fail because of him he gave
poor old unle Chuck a real doozy and now
we're the ones paying for it that blue
[__]
enemy away from
[Applause]
[Music]
come on boys let's pee in the hole so he
drowns play
Mr chuck would you kindly give my big
Sonic the Hedgehog this time serving of
Creme Brule I made it to celebrate him
graduating Middle School Sonic didn't
grad well can't you give it to him
anyway he is a growing boy and I want
him to know that whether he succeeds or
not I will always be there for
him hey son
special
delivery excuse me ma'am smoking is not
permitted here on school
grounds here's an idea pal how about you
mind your own and business I paid a lot
of dollars for these and it's my baby
girl's big day so I'm not going to let
anyone especially some glorified babies
s to kill my vibe
go back to your little classroom and
have yourself one of those siss pizza
parties oh look there's my daughter
doesn't she look adorable in her
graduation gown yeah she really does
she's the same color as a pickle if
pickles were pink instead of green I
guess you could call her a pinkle ha haa
have you ever seen anyone as gorgeous as
her she's like a mve star up there well
I wouldn't go that far I mean seriously
look at her she's not just cute she's
down right sexy look look she's looking
at me mama loves you dear Mommy loves
you I don't know
this so going to don't know they found
your restraining order damn it I said
put it in your
sock your
kids because stupid what do you mean
they won't graduate Sonia has worked so
hard she's gotten straight A all
year no
think I'm going to meet my boyfriend at
the Taco Bell
forkas
oh
back with the rest of thex
says but but our entire class failed
what's the point in cheering if there's
no one to cheer for that's not
me yeah [__] you're not graduating
doesn't mean you don't have a role to
play here you're a cheerleader my
cheerleader fat [__] shake your ass for
me [__] I want to see you shake it like
a salt
shaker well girls let's get this ball
rolling for tummy
they're playing the
song wish they we're playing it for
us hey guys I know this sucks but at
least we've got each other you know what
I reckon Old Yeller is right we may not
be graduating tonight but we've still
got each other and I think that's pretty
dang special did you hear that Knuckles
that means you and we gets to spend
another year together
[Music]
stop it
St face it Charles hatred will never win
in the face of friendship
[Music]